Profile:

A young determined professional with a strong desire to grow and learn. I have a combined four years' experience in the consumer packaged goods, the auto manufacturing, and restaurant industries. I am now looking for a new career opportunity in a dynamic organization with room for advancement.

Work Experience:

Administrative Associate II, P&G Team, Metro Richelieu.Inc dedicated. 2015-2016 CROSSMARK Canada

Responsibilities:

- Managed client (P&G) accounts and provided administrative support to CROSSMARK Metro Inc. Quebec and Ontario Sales Team, ensuring Client, Customer and Company expectations were met
- Liaised between client, customer, and account Executives on daily tasks and requests.
- Generated and executed legally-binding customer contracts.
 - o Cost Sheets, Deal sheets, LPI/LPR forms.
- Consolidated, recapped and distributed customer deductions to the field sales team in order to facilitate reconciliation within the allotted time frame.
- Complied with company and client expectations relating to fund management.
- Prepared work orders for new store openings, including fixtures and merchandising (Cosmetics).
- Debit reconciliation through P&G's customer fund management program (CFM).

Accomplishments:

- Replaced a senior sales representative covering APDO, PCC, Hair care, Skin care, Cosmetics, and Hair colour categories for 3 months while simultaneously performing administrative tasks.
- I created and maintained an ongoing excel tracker for valid and invalid liquidations deducted by Metro Banners. The tracker directly resulted in a significant refund for invalid liquidation deductions.
- I audited and corrected multiple CFM programs in order to comply with P&G stewardship guidelines.
- I willingly assumed additional responsibility as required support my team and client.

Production Support Supervisor 2014-2015 Waterville TG inc.

- Ensured the company policies and mandates were followed by unionized workers.
- Led a team of 10 unionized personnel.
- Quality control: Audited and verified internal control documents.
- Made out work orders, and purchase orders with SAP.
- Ensured the prevention of work place accidents by applying the collective agreement and following CSST standards.
- Provided support to the workers, and supervisors.
- Handled multiple projects at once.

Production Supervisor 2014 (Temp)

Waterville TG inc.

- Worked a swing shift (every week switched shifts: day, evening, nights).
- Followed the directions of the Production Director, while compiling to the company's quality standards.
- Led different teams of 25-30 unionized personnel.
- Held team members accountable to the collective agreement and CSST regulations.
- Provided support to the workers, in a problem solving capacity (production quotas, break downs).
- Audited the production performance of all team members under my direct supervision.
- Followed the principles of the Toyota Production Systems (5S, Kaizen principles).

Teaching Assistant (Occupational Health and Safety) 2013-2014 Bishop's University

- Supported students when they were having difficulty with course material.
- Oversaw and corrected exams.

Assistant Manager, 2009-2011 Peps Restaurant (JR Pépin inc.)

- Led a team of four members.
 - Interviewed candidates, and selected new employees.
 - Handled customer complaints and suggestions.
 - Kept basic book keeping and "cashed out" the register each close of business.

Education:

Bachelors in Business Administration

Concentration in Human Resources
William's School of Business, Bishop's University, Sherbrooke Qc



2014

Diplôme d'études collégiales

*Pre-commerce (business) program*Champlain College Lennoxville, Sherbrooke Qc.



2010

Competences

- Bilingual (English/ French).
- Coordinated and conducted team meetings.
- Strong organization and follow up skills.
- Ability to problem solve and work with colleagues and clients to find win-win solutions.
- Drafting and proof reading in English (4 years)
- Strong communication skills.

- Microsoft Power Point (19 years' experience)
- Microsoft Word (17 years' experience)
- Microsoft Excel (9 years' experience)
 - Vlookup (everyday user)
- Microsoft Outlook (9 years' experience)
- SAP (1 year of experience)
- CFM (1 year of experience)
- Data entry (6 months of experience)
- GS1 ECCnet (1 year of experience)
- Class 5 driver's license